welcome back to another kiddin live
欢迎回到另一个孩子的现场直播
video editing tutorial in the last video
上一个视频中的视频编辑教程
we looked at using the obscure effect to
我们看到了使用模糊效果来
kind of obscure out a license plate but
有点模糊了车牌 但是
the problem was when we moved forward in
问题是当我们向前推进时
our video that would that box would kind
我们的录像带就是那个盒子
of just stay in the same place and it
只是呆在同一个地方 它
was going up and like see it would have
正在上升 就像你看到的那样
obscuring part of the Mercedes symbol
遮挡梅赛德斯标志的一部分
there and so this box just sort of
这个箱子就像是
stayed wherever we put it and so now I'm
不管我们把它放在哪里 所以现在我
going to show you how to have that box
我会告诉你怎么拿到那个盒子
move and kind of track along with a
移动和某种轨迹沿着一个
certain object in the video in theory so
从理论上讲 视频中的某些对象
I will say this tool is not perfect by
我会说这个工具并不完美 因为
any means but it's actually called Auto
任何手段 但它实际上被称为汽车
mask under blur and hide so we'll drag
蒙版下的模糊和隐藏 这样我们就可以拖动
it in and what the auto mask will do you
以及自动面罩会对你造成什么影响
choose a point in the video that you
在视频中选择您认为
think is a good reference point and you
思考是一个很好的参照点 而你
just resize this box so it looks very
只需调整这个框的大小 使其看起来非常
similar to the obscure so we'll just set
类似于默默无闻 所以我们只需设置
this to a point that we want to kind of
这一点是我们想要的
maybe like right here so we'll set it to
也许就在这里 所以我们要把它设置成
that license plate and then we actually
那个车牌 然后我们实际上
have this analyze button we click
让我们点击这个分析按钮
analyze and it takes just a second it
分析一下 只需一秒钟
analyzes kind of all the pixels within
分析内部所有像素的种类
that box and it does its best to try and
那个盒子 它会尽最大努力
follow them throughout so now if we go
从头到尾跟着他们 所以如果我们走了
forward it should so that box is still
应将其转发 以便该框仍然存在
moving up but look it's not obscuring
往上走 但看起来并不模糊
the Mercedes symbol if we click off so
梅赛德斯标志 如果我们点击关闭
that red box is no longer selected now
那个红色方框现在不再被选中
we see it's following along as best it
我们看到它是最好的跟随者
can with that license plate and it
带着那个车牌的罐头和它
doesn't now it tracks over to the right
现在它不是向右移动了吗
so it kind of messed up there but at
所以它有点搞砸了 但在
least there's no it's not going up and
至少不会 它不会上升
getting that Mercedes symbol like it was
把梅赛德斯标志弄得像以前一样
doing last time we can fix that I think
上次我们可以解决这个问题 我想
by just making this box a little bit
只要把这个盒子做一点
bigger then we were hit analyze and I
比我们被分析和我击中的更大
think that should be good now and we'll
我觉得现在应该很好了 我们会
just merge the data together so let's
只需将数据合并在一起 让我们
see what it does now so that's better
看看它现在做了什么 这样就更好了
and so now we have it going start from
所以现在我们要从
the beginning it kind of you know
从一开始你就知道
obscures that license plate and it
模糊了车牌和它
doesn't get up and cover up the Mercedes
不会站起来遮盖梅赛德斯
symbol though so this is sort of a
符号 所以这是一种
working example to tell you the truth I
实事求是地告诉你 工作的例子是
tried to get lots of other video footage
我试着拿到很多其他的视频片段
like if we go later on this video here
比如 如果我们稍后在这段视频中继续
I'll delete this now I couldn't get it
我现在要删除这个 我拿不到
to even try
甚至想尝试一下
to this part so it's not even it's not
这一部分 所以它甚至不是
super great yet but it is an option that
非常好 但这是一个选择
might just work for you as long as your
可能只会为你工作 只要你
subject or the thing you're trying to
主题或你想要做的事情
obscure is not moving too much you might
默默无闻是不会移动太多你可能
have success but don't if you don't get
取得成功 但如果你得不到
frustrated if you can't get it to work
如果你不能让它工作 你会感到沮丧
because it's a it's not a very good
因为这不是一个很好的
tracking tool if you want to do more
如果您想做更多事情 请使用跟踪工具
advanced tracking like this I would
像这样的高级跟踪 我会
recommend using a free software like
推荐使用免费软件 如
Natron you can check out my other
纳特隆 你可以看看我的另一个
tutorials in fact I'll make a tutorial
教程事实上 我会做一个教程
in there about how to do obscure and
在那里关于如何做晦涩的和
actually track really well to obscure an
实际上很好地跟踪以遮蔽一个
object hopefully you found this kind of
希望你能找到这种
informative though appreciate you
虽然消息灵通 但很感谢你
watching and I'll see you in the next
看着我 我们下一天见
video
视频